# KARYNA MISNIK

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# **CONTACT INFO**



+358 45 2542500



karinamisnik94@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/karyna-misnik-542945247/



https://karynamisnik.github.io/karyna/



Helsinki, Finland

# **EDUCATION**

#### 2010-2015

Philologist, teacher of English and English literature, English translator

Vitebsk State University named after P.M. Masherov

## 2020-

**Software Developer** Omnia Vocational school

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Belarusian

Russian

Finnish(beginner)

## **PROFILE**

I finished Vitebsk University in Belarus. I got a degree in English Philology. After that I mostly worked in educational sphere. In 2019 I moved to Finland. During my first year I decide to make a career change from education to IT. I am a curious, very honest and reliable person.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### 2020

Kielo International school Teacher assistant, substitute English teacher (Integration training)

## 2018-2019

Panda English School English teacher

## 2017-2019

Zaochnik.com Scientific consultant

### 2015-2017

Orsha State school №2 English teacher

# **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, PHP, SQL, JAVA

# **INTERESTS**



Gaming



Hiking



Painting



Rock festivals



rasting Beer



DIY